Mss.B.H97p
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Letter to Colonel Clem[en]t Biddle, Dec. 27, 1787; Hutchinson, James, 1752-1793
    Xerox copy of A.L. in 3rd. P. 1p. and end. From original in Charles Roberts autograph collection, Haverford College. Asks to borrow ten dollars.
  - Letter to [Mrs.] Katherine [Rickey Hutchinson] Milnor, April 28, 1789; 13x8-1/4; Hutchinson, James, 1752-1793
    A.L.S. 2p. Family news. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to James Hutchinson, Philadelphia, March 30, 1790; 9-1/2x7-1/2; Hiester, Daniel, 1747-1804
    New York, A.L.S. 1p. and add. Concerning assumption of state debts by the federal government.
  - Letter to [James] Hutchinson, Philadelphia, July 7, 1790; 10x8; Hiester, Daniel, 1747-1804
    A.L.S. 1p. and add. Question of residence (of the U.S. capital?).
  - Receipted bill to [Rodolph] Tillier, Dec., 1790; 4x6-3/4; Kuhn, Adam, 1741-1817
    D.S.: For Dr. Kuhn, Robert G. Davidson. 1p. and add., end. Medical bill.
  - Opinion on law of payment of veterans of the Revolution, June 21, 1791; 13-1/2x8; Lewis, William, 1745?-1822
    Philadelphia, A.D.S. 2p.
  - Letter to [James] Hutchinson, July 29, 1791; 9-1/4x7-1/4; Irwin, Nathaniel, 1746-1812
    A.L.S. 2p. and add. Concerning recommendations to the governor for a vacancy on the bench.
  - Letter to James Hutchinson, Philadelphia, Aug. 17, 1791; 8-1/4x6-3/4; Ewing, John, 1732-1802
    Harrisburg, A.L.S. 2p. and add. Describes distressing condition of Nancy and her illness.
  - Certificate of membership to James Hutchinson, Oct. 6, 1792; 10-3/4x15; Pennsylvania Society for Promoting the Abolition of Slavery
    Philadelphia, Printed D. filled in in ms. S.: Jam[e]s Pemberton, et al. 1p.
  - Letter to William Shippen and James Hutchinson, Feb. 7, 1793; 12-3/4x7-3/4; United States. War Department
    A.L.S.: Jo[h]n Stagg, Jr., Chief Clerk. 1p. and add. Asks that they certify John Blackburn for a pension.
  - Letter to [James] Hutchinson, Aug. 1, 1793; 8x6-3/4; Caldwell, Charles, 1772-1853
    A.L.S. 3p. and add. Asks to become a member of the "Democratic Society of Pennsylvania."
  - Letter to James Hutchinson, Aug. 24, 1793; 12-1/2x7-1/2; Rush, Benjamin, 1746-1813
    A.L.S. 1p. and add. Announces epidemic of yellow fever in Philadelphia.
  - Extract of Minutes for mourning the loss of James Hutchinson in a yellow fever epidemic, Nov. 25, 1793 - Oct. 4, 1853; 12x9-3/4; Pennsylvania Hospital
    A.D.S.: Wm. G. Malin, steward. 1p.
  - Mortgage to H. G. Clay and Charles H. Hutchinson, Oct. 2, 1867 - Jan. 29, 1872; 7-1/4x9-3/4; McKean and Elk Land and Improvement Company
    Printed D. filled in in ms. S. by officers of the company. 11 items, with stamps and seals.
  - Receipt to Charles H. Hutchinson for $307.12, Oct. 24, 1868; 8x5; McKean and Elk Land and Improvement Company
    Philadelphia, D.S. by treasurer. 1p. and end. Stamp.
  - Purchase of shares of Charels H. Hutchinson for land, Nov.17, 1870 - June 17, 1871; McKean and Elk Land and Improvement Company
    Printed D. filled in in ms.S. by the treasurer. 3 items.
  - Letter to James P. Hutchinson, Philadelphia, Sept. 10, 1928; 10-1/2x7-1/4; Hutchinson, S. Pemberton (Sydney Pemberton), 1861-1929
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. Presents letters of Hutchinson to Pemberton and suggests they be presented to the APS.
  - Letter to Thomas Mifflin, undated; 13-1/4x8-1/4; Hiester, Joseph, 1752-1832
    Philadelphia. A.L.S. 1p. and add. Does not think General St. Clair will get votes for the governorship.
  - Address leaves, undated; Hutchinson, James, 1752-1793
    Scraps, to Mrs. Katherine Milnor and Israel Pemberton. A.D. 4 items. Various sizes.
  - Letter to Mrs. Sarah Shaw, undated; 8-3/4x7-1/4; Hutchinson, James, 1752-1793
    A.L.S. 2p. Incomplete. Business news. News of the war. Friendly letter.